<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dalilaprile.it/projects/</link><description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 22:05:50 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dalilaprile.it/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Carecloud</title><link>https://dalilaprile.it/projects/carecloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 22:05:50 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dalilaprile.it/projects/carecloud/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="the-goal">The goal&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The development of an &lt;strong>Electronic Medical Record system&lt;/strong> based on a Software as a Service (SaaS) architecture will enable &lt;strong>patients&amp;rsquo; medical records&lt;/strong> to be &lt;strong>created and managed digitally&lt;/strong>, allow them to be &lt;strong>consulted continuously&lt;/strong>, provide &lt;strong>secure and controlled access&lt;/strong> to information for authorized personnel, facilitate &lt;strong>efficient data sharing&lt;/strong> among the providers involved, and ensure &lt;strong>full compliance&lt;/strong> with &lt;strong>data protection regulations (GDPR)&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-problem">The problem&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Currently, in many &lt;strong>healthcare facilities&lt;/strong>, &lt;strong>patient records&lt;/strong> are predominantly managed through paper-based or non-integrated digital systems, resulting in &lt;strong>slow and difficult access&lt;/strong> to &lt;strong>clinical information&lt;/strong> for both &lt;strong>patients&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>healthcare professionals&lt;/strong>, &lt;strong>increased risk&lt;/strong> of &lt;strong>data loss&lt;/strong> or &lt;strong>damage&lt;/strong>, &lt;strong>inefficient sharing&lt;/strong> of information among medical staff, a &lt;strong>higher likelihood of errors&lt;/strong> due to &lt;strong>incomplete&lt;/strong> or &lt;strong>outdated data&lt;/strong>, and greater challenges in ensuring &lt;strong>privacy protection&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>regulatory compliance&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Exchangify App</title><link>https://dalilaprile.it/projects/exchangify-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dalilaprile.it/projects/exchangify-app/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="the-goal">The Goal&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The goal of this app is to provide travelers with a &lt;strong>seamless&lt;/strong> solution for managing &lt;strong>currency exchanges&lt;/strong> by offering &lt;strong>real-time&lt;/strong> exchange rate information and helping them locate &lt;strong>ATMs&lt;/strong> with the lowest withdrawal &lt;strong>fees&lt;/strong> in foreign countries.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By simplifying access to up-to-date currency data and reducing hidden costs, the app aims to enhance the &lt;strong>travel experience&lt;/strong>, empowering users to make informed financial decisions and minimize expenses while abroad.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-problem">The problem&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Travelers often face &lt;strong>challenges&lt;/strong> when managing currency exchanges during their trips, including fluctuating exchange rates, hidden fees, and difficulty finding ATMs that offer reasonable withdrawal fees in &lt;strong>foreign countries&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Exchangify Website</title><link>https://dalilaprile.it/projects/exchangify-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dalilaprile.it/projects/exchangify-website/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="the-challenge">The Challenge&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Travelers often find it difficult to access &lt;strong>real-time&lt;/strong> and accurate currency &lt;strong>exchange rates&lt;/strong> while on the go. This can lead to confusion and potential financial loss due to unfavorable exchange rates.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Also finding an &lt;strong>ATM&lt;/strong> that charges reasonable withdrawal fees in a foreign location is a common challenge. Travelers may end up paying &lt;strong>high fees&lt;/strong> due to a lack of information about more affordable options nearby.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-solution">The Solution&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Exchangify is designed to empower travelers of &lt;strong>all ages&lt;/strong> by simplifying the complexities associated with currency exchange and ATM &lt;strong>withdrawals&lt;/strong> abroad. By addressing these common pain points, the platform aims to enhance the &lt;strong>travel experience&lt;/strong>, reduce financial stress, and promote informed &lt;strong>financial decisions&lt;/strong> while on the move.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>